<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Quora文选</title>
  
  
  <link href="http://example.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://example.com/"/>
  <updated>2022-03-10T03:01:06.676Z</updated>
  <id>http://example.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Quorra</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What is the key for a healthy relationship</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/03/09/2022-03-09-What-is-the-key-for-a-healthy-relationship/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/03/09/2022-03-09-What-is-the-key-for-a-healthy-relationship/</id>
    <published>2022-03-09T13:04:53.939Z</published>
    <updated>2022-03-10T03:01:06.676Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="What-is-the-key-for-a-healthy-relationship"><strong>What is the key for a healthy relationship</strong></h4><p><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'><em><strong>Kale Hyder</strong></em>,  Disabled cat dad</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'>76.7K views · 2.3K Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><ul><li><strong>You and your partner equally give and take.</strong> Some days, your partner may be extra busy or unusually stressed. You should step up by making dinner, doing the chores, and asking them what they need. When you find yourself in a similar state, your partner should step up like you did.</li><li><strong>You address disagreements immediately.</strong> You don’t <u>brush them under the rug</u>. You engage in difficult conversations and find common ground to move forward.</li><li><strong>You never go to bed upset with your partner.</strong> You take time to resolve any conflicts before bed, even if it takes an hour. By resolving the conflict, you both feel better and subsequently give each other the best <u>snuggles</u> and <u>cuddles</u>.</li><li><strong>You find time to connect each day.</strong> You eat dinner together. You snuggle on the couch while you watch a show. You do something each day to reconnect and grow your love.</li><li><strong>You identify their love language.</strong> Do they <u>crave</u> physical touch or words of <u>affirmation</u>? You should identify the type of love they respond best to and provide it.</li></ul><p>My girlfriend and I follow these rules, which has caused our relationship to flourish.</p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>待更新<br></span></p></details><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong>Greg Grigorian:</strong></em><br>I think it’s better to be single a lot of the time because relationships cause more drama than pleasure.</p><p><em><strong>Robyn T</strong></em>:<br>Fantastic advice, thank you. I hope you two will continue making these important daily.</p></blockquote><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>rug</strong>: a piece of thick cloth or wool that covers part of a floor, used for warmth or as a decoration 小地毯</li><li><strong>brush (something) under the rug</strong>: to ignore, deny, or conceal from public view or knowledge something that is embarrassing, unappealing, or damaging to one’s reputation 忽视、否认或隐瞒一些令人尴尬、不愉快或有损个人声誉的事情，不为公众所知</li><li><strong>snuggle</strong>: /'snʌgl/ to settle into a warm comfortable position 依偎，〔舒服地〕蜷伏</li><li><strong>cuddle</strong>: /'kʌdl/ to hold someone or something very close to you with your arms around them, especially to show that you love them〔尤指表示喜爱而〕抱，拥抱，搂抱</li><li><strong>crave</strong>: to have an extremely strong desire for something 渴望，热望</li><li><strong>affirmation</strong>: affirming 肯定; 断言: The poem is a joyous affirmation of the power of love. 这首诗以欢快的笔触肯定了爱情的力量。</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGdEqn">https://qr.ae/pGdEqn</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">My girlfriend and I follow these rules, which has caused our relationship to flourish.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
    <category term="爱情" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E7%88%B1%E6%83%85/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How do you respond when your child threatens to run away from home when they get in trouble?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/03/08/2022-03-08-How-do-you-respond-when-your-child-threatens-to-run-away-from-home-when-they-get-in-trouble/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/03/08/2022-03-08-How-do-you-respond-when-your-child-threatens-to-run-away-from-home-when-they-get-in-trouble/</id>
    <published>2022-03-08T13:58:31.037Z</published>
    <updated>2022-03-10T03:10:34.422Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="How-do-you-respond-when-your-child-threatens-to-run-away-from-home-when-they-get-in-trouble"><a href="#How-do-you-respond-when-your-child-threatens-to-run-away-from-home-when-they-get-in-trouble" class="headerlink" title="How do you respond when your child threatens to run away from home when they get in trouble?"></a><strong>How do you respond when your child threatens to run away from home when they get in trouble?</strong></h4><p><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'><em><strong>Laurie Keller</strong></em>, former University Senior Lecturer Computer Science</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'>153.8K views · 5.1K Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>My brother, then about 5 years old, got really annoyed at my parents and said he was going to run away.</p><p>“Fine,” my mother said with a sweet smile. “I’ll help you pack.”</p><p>She and my dad did indeed help my brother pack a little suitcase and walked him to the front door.</p><p>At that point he stopped. Everyone could smell dinner cooking.</p><p>With a tear in his eye, he asked, “Can I wait until after dinner?”</p><p>“Of course,” my parents said. “Have dinner first, and then run away.”</p><p>We had dinner, by the end of which my brother had somehow managed to return his suitcase to his room and unpack it, and <strong>everyone pretended not to remember that there was a plan to run away.</strong></p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>待更新</span></p></details><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong>Helena Humbridge:</strong></em><br>When I was 6, I told my dad I was running away from home. I used my favorite Snoopy towel and I put in some clothes, toys and cookies.</p><p>Dad watched me tie up my towel and he told me to live in the outside world I would need money. I said I’ll get a job. Not a lot of people hire 6 year olds. I would be better off finishing school then getting a job then leaving.</p><p>I agreed my dad had the right idea. As an adult, I knew my dad was <u>playing along</u>. And I knew why I asked him and not mom. My mom wasn’t as patient with me, she would have yelled at me and probably <u>smacked</u> me. Dad knew I was just angry for the moment.</p><p>The lesson I took away from this was <strong>not to question someone when they are upset, try to offer an alternative that was safer</strong>. It helped me a lot raising my kids.</p></blockquote><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>play along</strong>: to pretend to agree to do what someone wants, in order to avoid annoying them or to get an advantage 假装顺从，暂且附和</li><li><strong>smack</strong>: &#x2F;smæk&#x2F; to hit someone, especially a child, with your open hand in order to punish them 用巴掌打，掴〔小孩，以示惩罚〕</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGdzzK">https://qr.ae/pGdzzK</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">everyone pretended not to remember that there was a plan to run away</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What disgusts you?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/03/08/2022-03-08-What-disgusts-you/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/03/08/2022-03-08-What-disgusts-you/</id>
    <published>2022-03-08T00:45:35.972Z</published>
    <updated>2022-03-08T03:54:30.596Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="What-disgusts-you"><a href="#What-disgusts-you" class="headerlink" title="What disgusts you?"></a><strong>What disgusts you?</strong></h4><p><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'><em><strong>Tessa Peterson</strong></em>, Aspiring writer</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'>247.1K views · 13.5K Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>I’ve heard a lot of men complain and say, “Oh my God. Why do women always date the worst kind of men? It’s so annoying.”</p><p>Well, I have the answer. It’s because we were lied to. Our entire childhood was a lie.</p><p>I remember that in <u>pre-school</u>, I was playing on the <u>swing set</u> of our school playground when suddenly, this boy named Liam (he was 4 years old) just walked over to me and pushed me off the swings without saying a WORD. He laughed and I just walked away. I had <u>scratches</u> all over my arms and legs and my face was covered with dirt.</p><p>It was my first time getting physically <u>bullied</u> during school and I was on the verge of tears the rest of the day. When I walked home, I cried to my mom and explained the entire thing to her. And you know what she said?</p><p>“Oh it’s okay, Tessa. He just <u>has a crush on</u> you.”</p><p>And from that day on, I was taught from the ripe age of 4 years old to confuse violence and affection. And if you’re a woman, I’m guessing you were taught that too. If you weren’t, you’re lucky.</p><p>Because resulting from that, I became attracted to <u>abusive</u> men.</p><p>Is that my fault? No.</p><p>Did I have to <u>unlearn</u> that? YES.</p><p>But instead of complaining about why women like certain types of men, maybe <strong>you should teach your kids that men shouldn’t be treating women poorly.</strong> We need to hold those boys accountable for their actions. No more “boys will be boys” bullshit.</p><p>And we need to teach women not to ignore this type of abuse at such a young age. It’s unacceptable.</p><p>Edit 1: It happens to boys too, not just girls! This is not a gender specific issue at all.</p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>待更新</span></p></details><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong>Kate Hayes:</strong></em><br>I remember in elementary school the rule was: If a boy hits you or is mean to you that means he is too shy to tell you that he likes you. But if a boy is nice to you it means he only wants to <u>get into your pants</u>.</p><p>How do you win? I just told my daughter that if a boy hit her to slug him back twice as hard and I would handle it. No boy ever hit her (lucky for them).</p></blockquote><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>pre-school</strong>: a school for children between two and five years of age〔二到五岁孩子的〕幼儿园，同义词：kindergarten</li><li><strong>swing set</strong>: a tall metal frame with swings hanging from it, for children to play on〔儿童玩耍的〕成套秋千</li><li><strong>scratch</strong>: a small cut on someone’s skin〔某人皮肤上的〕划痕，划伤: There were deep scratches all over her face. 她脸上全是很深的划痕。</li><li><strong>bully</strong>: to threaten to hurt someone or frighten them, especially someone smaller or weaker 欺侮，恐吓 〔尤指以大欺小，恃强凌弱〕</li><li><strong>have a crush on</strong>: to have a feeling of romantic love for someone, especially someone you do not know well 热恋…，迷恋…〔尤指对不大熟识的人〕</li><li><strong>abusive</strong>: (of speech or a person) criticizing harshly and rudely; insulting （指言语或人）责骂的, 辱骂的</li><li><strong>unlearn</strong>: informal to deliberately forget something you have learned, in order to change the way you do something 设法忘记，抛弃〔已学会的东西〕</li><li><strong>get into one’s pants</strong>: slang To have sex with one. (Usually said of the intention or expectation.)</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGdmx3">https://qr.ae/pGdmx3</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">It happens to boys too, not just girls! This is not a gender specific issue at all.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What are some psychological facts about love</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/03/07/2022-03-07-What-are-some-psychological-facts-about-love/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/03/07/2022-03-07-What-are-some-psychological-facts-about-love/</id>
    <published>2022-03-07T07:04:29.700Z</published>
    <updated>2022-03-07T12:58:57.746Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="What-are-some-psychological-facts-about-love"><strong>What are some psychological facts about love</strong></h4><p><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'><em><strong>Suhail Hany</strong></em>,  Dating Researcher</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'>1.4M views · 16.3K Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><ol><li><strong>Women love details</strong>: Instead of saying “You are beautiful” say:<ul><li>I like your hair.</li><li>You have a really great sense of fashion.</li></ul></li><li><strong>Confidence beats EVERYTHING</strong>: even beats looks, money and personality. So, Pretend to be confident even if you aren’t, at least in front of your crush. Keep eye contact with everyone and you will appear a lot more confident.</li><li><strong>A guy capable of fixing things and cooking is sexy</strong>: this was reported by many women.</li><li>Busy men/women are a lot attractive: Do things that you love and don’t be free 24/7.</li><li>If your crush doesn’t react well try limiting your time with her: disappearing for a while making her miss you and think about you, but never overdo this because it will make the situation worse.</li><li>A good smell is very underrated: get rid of smoking, take showers, brush your teeth and put some perfume. And you will see magnificent results.</li><li>A watch on your wrist makes you hotter: It makes you look organized and mature.</li></ol><p>Looks and money are important and improves Attraction a lot. But believe me, a confident average looking man is more attractive than insecure handsome man. Non confident men look weak, and being a weak man is a very <u>turn off</u>.</p><p>So to sum up: <strong>Dress well, smell good, have a good career and appear strong and confident and watch the Awesome Results.</strong></p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>待更新</span></p></details><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong>Oleg Romanov:</strong></em><br>I’m no expert on relationships, but from my few experiences, I’m starting to wonder about the assumptions I heard as a teen in regards to attracting women. Like “girls like jerks/assholes” or “ignore her and she’ll want you more”.</p><p>While in a limited number of cases these may be true, overall they seem like an <u>ingenious</u> attempt at explaining the ideas mentioned in the answer.</p><p>I remember learning this myself. When I voluntarily acted like a jerk to my then girlfriend, she just said “asshole!” and we didn’t speak for a while. That was a lifelong lesson. Such a statement is probably an overcorrection of the whole “nice guy problem”, which, again, quite simply, is about the problem of expecting something from a woman just for being “nice” to her.</p><p>And the ignoring part is just about not seeming (or actually not being) needy to the point of obsession. Everyone begins to feel smothered at some point, and it becomes rather uncomfortable. It really goes for both parties. Relying on the other person for personal fulfillment rather than actually having a life and goals makes the relationship tasteless and redundant.</p><p>Anyway, thanks for a good answer.</p></blockquote><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>turn sb. off</strong>: to make someone feel that they are not attracted to you in a sexual way使丧失性兴趣，反义词: turn on</li><li><strong>ingenious</strong>: /ɪn’dʒinɪəs/ an ingenious plan, idea, or object works well and is the result of clever thinking and new ideas〔计划、主意或物体〕精巧的，巧妙的</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGdSAr">https://qr.ae/pGdSAr</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">Dress well, smell good, have a good career and appear strong and confident and watch the Awesome Results.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Is the president of Ukraine a comedian?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/03/06/2022-03-06-Is-the-president-of-Ukraine-a-comedian/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/03/06/2022-03-06-Is-the-president-of-Ukraine-a-comedian/</id>
    <published>2022-03-06T09:54:12.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-03-06T10:26:17.038Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="Is-the-president-of-Ukraine-a-comedian"><a href="#Is-the-president-of-Ukraine-a-comedian" class="headerlink" title="Is the president of Ukraine a comedian?"></a><strong>Is the president of Ukraine a comedian?</strong></h4><p><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);"><em><strong>Eric Wicklund</strong></em>, Former Operations Specialist at United States Navy (USN) (1984–1992)Fri</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);">19.3k Views · 1.5k Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>He used to be.</p><p>In fact, he starred in a TV series where he played the Ukrainian President.</p><p>I’ll bet he never expected what would come next. I guess it helps to practice first. He’s doing a terrific job of motivating and leading his people.</p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>待更新</span></p></details><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong>Bridgett Mazin</strong></em>:</p><p>In fact, I think Ukraine is more about him and the <u>oligarchs</u> selling out their territory and the Ukrainian people will suffer the consequences, but he can’t give up or death will greet him! The main thing is that Ukraine was the first to challenge Russia, so the West’s <u>propaganda</u> was directed against it</p><p><em><strong>Preston Parranto:</strong></em><br>He is truly a hero. I don’t even care what he did before this crisis. What he’s doing now shows what a hero he is!</p><blockquote><p><em><strong>Cass Dean:</strong></em><br>He is no hero. He is safe himself. He is placing his citizens in <u>peril</u> for a few extra tens of thousands on his weekly bonus. Throwing civilians into the path of <u>rampaging</u> armed <u>mobs</u> is not brave. He had an opportunity to get his country out from under the role of U.S. Patsy and first to take fire if a war breaks out. But he is Igor Kolomoisky’s boy toy and those weren’t his orders.</p></blockquote><p><strong>Eric Wicklund:</strong><br>US has actors become President. Ronald Reagan was a professional actor. Donald Trump a reality TV star.</p></blockquote><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>oligarch</strong>: &#x2F;‘ɑlə’gɑrk&#x2F; a member of a small group of people who run a country or organization 寡头政治家; 寡头统治集团成员</li><li><strong>propaganda</strong>: &#x2F;‘prɑpə’gændə&#x2F; information which is false or which emphasizes just one part of a situation, used by a government or political group to make people agree with them〔政府或政党为了影响民意的〕宣传</li><li><strong>peril</strong>: &#x2F;‘pɛrəl&#x2F; great danger, especially of being harmed or killed 巨大的危险</li><li><strong>rampage</strong>: &#x2F;‘ræmpedʒ&#x2F; to rush about in groups, acting in a wild or violent way 横冲直撞</li><li><strong>mob</strong>: a large noisy crowd, especially one that is angry and violent〔成群的〕暴民，乱民:</li></ul></blockquote>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">1</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Quora" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/"/>
    
    <category term="文选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
    <category term="一句话网站" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E4%B8%80%E5%8F%A5%E8%AF%9D%E7%BD%91%E7%AB%99/"/>
    
    <category term="安卓" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E5%AE%89%E5%8D%93/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What does China look like in the eyes of the US government?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/03/05/2022-03-05-What-does-China-look-like-in-the-eyes-of-the-US-government/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/03/05/2022-03-05-What-does-China-look-like-in-the-eyes-of-the-US-government/</id>
    <published>2022-03-05T11:51:52.743Z</published>
    <updated>2022-03-09T13:53:49.838Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="What-does-China-look-like-in-the-eyes-of-the-US-government"><strong>What does China look like in the eyes of the US government?</strong></h4><p><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'><em><strong>Mia Brown</strong></em>,  Master World Literatures &amp; Chinese</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'>8.7K views · 1.7K Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>In the eyes of the U.S. government, China is a country with rapid economic and military growth that is about to threaten U.S. <u>hegemony</u>.</p><p>In recent years, with the gradual growth of China’s economic and military power, The U.S. government regards China as an attack target and keeps spreading rumors and has been <u>advocating</u> the “China threat” to the outside world. It advocates that China will become the world’s superpower and threaten the security of other countries with its continuous rapid economic growth.</p><p>Because the United States is afraid that the position of “America First” will not be maintained, it <u>fantasizes</u> that China will become a country with strong economic and military power.</p><p>The US is decades ahead of China in military power and has instead created the appearance that China is threatening their military power.</p><p>In fact, China is only making weapons for self-defense.</p><p><strong>America is the key to world peace and stability.</strong></p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>待更新</span></p></details><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong>Dongxu Li:</strong></em><br>I’d criticize more on the fact that how the US wasted so much of their money on bullying tiny nations through endless wars or leading the world into a new worldwide military competition as the world leader.</p></blockquote><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>hegemony</strong>: /hɪ’dʒɛmoni/ a situation in which one state or country controls others〔一国对其他国的〕霸权，支配权</li><li><strong>advocate</strong>: to publicly say that something should be done 主张，拥护，鼓吹: Extremists were openly advocating violence. 极端主义者公开鼓吹使用暴力。</li><li><strong>fantasize</strong>: /'fæntəsaɪz/ to imagine that you are doing something which is very pleasant or exciting, but which is very unlikely to happen 想象，幻想</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGdOX6">https://qr.ae/pGdOX6</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">America is the key to world peace and stability.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Quora" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/"/>
    
    <category term="文选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why didn&#39;t Vladimir Putin wait until the warmer months to invade? Why now?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/03/05/2022-03-05-Why-didn&#39;t-Vladimir-Putin-wait-until-the-warmer-months-to-invade-Why-now/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/03/05/2022-03-05-Why-didn&#39;t-Vladimir-Putin-wait-until-the-warmer-months-to-invade-Why-now/</id>
    <published>2022-03-05T01:04:11.410Z</published>
    <updated>2022-03-05T02:22:33.884Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="Why-didn’t-Vladimir-Putin-wait-until-the-warmer-months-to-invade-Why-now"><a href="#Why-didn’t-Vladimir-Putin-wait-until-the-warmer-months-to-invade-Why-now" class="headerlink" title="Why didn’t Vladimir Putin wait until the warmer months to invade? Why now?"></a><strong>Why didn’t Vladimir Putin wait until the warmer months to invade? Why now?</strong></h4><p><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'><em><strong>Sylvain Saurel</strong></em>,  inbitcoinwetrust.substack.com at In Bitcoin We Trust (2017-present)</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'>253.4K views · 1.4K Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>Europe is highly dependent on Russian gas. However, it is in this winter period that Europe needs gas from Russia the most.</p><p>It is therefore now that the gas weapon is the most strategic for Putin.</p><p>I even think that Putin would have attacked Ukraine earlier without the Olympic Games in Beijing in February 2022.</p><p>During the summer, the Russian gas argument remains important to <u>replenish</u> <u>reserves</u> for the following winter, but this leaves more time to try to find alternative solutions, even if it is difficult.</p><p>If Putin cuts off Russian gas now to Europe in <u>retaliation</u> for the economic and financial <u>sanctions</u> against his country, the situation will be catastrophic for many European countries.</p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>待更新</span></p></details><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong>ubert Okari</strong></em>:<br>Putin is a reasonable person and won’t do that, however, if it were some politicians from the west, especially the US, they would have cut it without blinking an eye.</p><p>The action he took in Ukraine was a must for any reasonable leader because a one sided government had been using excessive force in the Eastern Ukraine against people who had a contrary political opinion and the Western politicians did nothing, except supply weapons to the government.</p><p>Even now, the Western countries don’t want to get to the root of Ukraine crisis, except label Russian as an <u>expansionist</u>.</p></blockquote><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>replenish</strong>: &#x2F;rɪ’plenɪʃ&#x2F; to put new supplies into something, or to fill something again 补充; 重新装满</li><li><strong>reserve</strong>: a supply of something kept to be used if it is needed 储备（物）: $10 million in cash reserves 1000万美元的现金储备</li><li><strong>retaliation</strong>: &#x2F;ri,tæli’eiʃən&#x2F; action against someone who has done something bad to you 报复，反击;</li><li><strong>sanctions</strong>: &#x2F;‘sæŋkʃən&#x2F; official orders or laws stopping trade, communication etc with another country, as a way of forcing its leaders to make political changes〔对某国的〕制裁</li><li><strong>expansionist</strong>: when a country or group increases the amount of land or power that they have – used especially to show disapproval 领土扩张（主义）的人〔尤含贬义〕</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGdwSv">https://qr.ae/pGdwSv</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">If Putin cuts off Russian gas now to Europe in retaliation for the economic and financial sanctions against his country, the situation will be catastrophic for many European countries.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Quora" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/"/>
    
    <category term="文选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What would you do if a passenger on an airplane demanded your seat so they could be next to a family member?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/03/05/2022-03-05-What-would-you-do-if-a-passenger-on-an-airplane-demanded-your-seat-so-they-could-be-next-to-a-family-member/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/03/05/2022-03-05-What-would-you-do-if-a-passenger-on-an-airplane-demanded-your-seat-so-they-could-be-next-to-a-family-member/</id>
    <published>2022-03-05T01:04:05.800Z</published>
    <updated>2022-03-06T04:15:30.614Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="What-would-you-do-if-a-passenger-on-an-airplane-demanded-your-seat-so-they-could-be-next-to-a-family-member"><a href="#What-would-you-do-if-a-passenger-on-an-airplane-demanded-your-seat-so-they-could-be-next-to-a-family-member" class="headerlink" title="What would you do if a passenger on an airplane demanded your seat so they could be next to a family member?"></a><strong>What would you do if a passenger on an airplane demanded your seat so they could be next to a family member?</strong></h4><p><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'><em><strong>Onne Vegter</strong></em>, owner of Wild Wings Safaris, specialist safari operator</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'>245.7K views ·  21.4K Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>I got to my seat on a <u>long haul</u> international flight to find a little boy sitting in my seat, next to his brother. It was the second row behind an emergency exit, meaning the row in front had only two seats (for mom and dad), and my seat had <u>legroom</u> (no seat in front of it).</p><p>I had paid extra for that specific seat because of the legroom. I’m 6’5 and can’t fit in a standard economy class seat.</p><p>The mom asked if the boy can sit there to be next to his brother (his assigned seat was in the middle section, opposite the aisle).</p><p>I said sure, as long as I can <u>swap</u> with you or your husband (they had emergency exit seats), as my long legs don’t fit in a standard seat which is why I paid extra for legroom.</p><p>She refused to give up her seat with legroom.</p><p><strong>So I politely refused her request.</strong></p><p>Mom got angry. Dad <u>grumbled</u> something <u>under his breath</u>.</p><p>Little boy pipes up: “It’s okay, mom, I don’t mind sitting in my own seat across the aisle.”</p><p><strong>That little <u>tyke</u> was the most mature person in that family.</strong></p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>待更新</span></p></details><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong>Gwen S:</strong></em><br>I feel for you! One of the last flights I was on, my seat mate was a very tall, well built man. Luckily, I’m a shorty, so I was able to give him some space to fit into his regular seat. He wasn’t comfortable, poor guy.</p></blockquote><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><p><strong>long&#x2F;slow haul</strong>: something that takes a lot of time and effort 耗时费力的事: At last we’ve won our freedom but it’s been a long bitter haul .我们终于赢得了自由，但这是通过漫长艰苦的努力才得来的。 </p></li><li><p><strong>legroom</strong>: space for your legs in front of the seats in a car, theatre etc〔汽车、戏院等座位前〕供伸腿的空间，腿部空间: There wasn’t enough leg room. 腿脚的活动空间不够大。</p></li><li><p><strong>swap</strong>: a situation in which you give something to someone and get another thing in return 交换，交易</p></li><li><p><strong>grumble</strong>: &#x2F;‘ɡrʌmbl&#x2F; to keep complaining in an unhappy way 不断地发牢骚，抱怨</p></li><li><p><strong>under one’s breath</strong>: in a quiet voice so that no one can hear you 低声地，压低嗓门地: ‘Son of a bitch’, he muttered under his breath. “”畜生” 他压低声音说。</p></li><li><p><strong>tyke</strong>: &#x2F;taɪk&#x2F; a child who is behaving badly 淘气的孩子，小淘气</p></li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGdw9Z">https://qr.ae/pGdw9Z</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">That little tyke was the most mature person in that family.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What overly simplistic life advice is deceptively effective if used correctly?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/03/04/2022-03-04-What-overly-simplistic-life-advice-is-deceptively-effective-if-used-correctly/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/03/04/2022-03-04-What-overly-simplistic-life-advice-is-deceptively-effective-if-used-correctly/</id>
    <published>2022-03-04T06:28:38.353Z</published>
    <updated>2022-03-06T04:15:24.349Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="What-overly-simplistic-life-advice-is-deceptively-effective-if-used-correctly"><a href="#What-overly-simplistic-life-advice-is-deceptively-effective-if-used-correctly" class="headerlink" title="What overly simplistic life advice is deceptively effective if used correctly?"></a><strong>What overly simplistic life advice is deceptively effective if used correctly?</strong></h4><p><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'><strong>Neman Ashraf</strong>, Police constable</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'>677.5K views · 12.7K Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>A man sitting in the hotel said to his friend “Look at that kid waiting tables, he’s so dumb that if I put 500 and 50 notes in front of him, he will pick up the fifty note…. let me show you.</p><p>He <u>hollered at</u> the kid, put both 500 and 50 bills at the table and said “Take a note of greater value out of these two”. When the child picked up the fifty note, they both laughed out loud and left, the child went back to his work.</p><p>Another person who sat besides and witnessed this, called the child afterwards and asked “You’re a grown kid who still doesn’t know the difference between fifty and five hundred notes. How come? That’s a loss”.</p><p>The child smiled and said “This man often comes here and demonstrates the same thing to his buddies for <u>kicks</u> and <u>giggles</u> to amuse over my stupidity as I pick up the note of fifty each time, they have a <u>momentary</u> laugh over this, but I get fifty. <strong>The day I picked 500 would be the day this game will be over and my income too</strong>.”</p><p>There is no need to be wise everywhere… especially when being wise affects one’s own peace, interests and happiness, then it is wise to become a fool.</p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>待更新</span></p></details><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Almarie-Meyer">Almarie Meyer</a></strong></p><p>The difference between long-term and short-term thinking. Companies often go wrong when they only think about their current year profits</p></blockquote><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>holler</strong>: to shout loudly 呼喊，大叫</li><li><strong>kick</strong>: something that you enjoy because it is exciting 极大的乐趣: get a kick out of &#x2F; from (doing): Gerald gets a kick out of dressing as a woman. 男扮女装给杰拉尔德带来极大乐趣。</li><li><strong>giggle</strong>: to laugh quickly, quietly, and in a high voice, because something is funny or because you are nervous or embarrassed 咯咯笑，傻笑</li><li><strong>momentary</strong>: &#x2F;‘məʊm(ə)nt(ə)rɪ&#x2F; continuing for a very short time 短暂的，瞬间的，片刻的</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGd4qt">https://qr.ae/pGd4qt</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">There is no need to be wise everywhere… especially when being wise affects one&#39;s own peace, interests and happiness, then it is wise to become a fool.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What made you smile today?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/03/03/2022-03-03-What-made-you-smile-today/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/03/03/2022-03-03-What-made-you-smile-today/</id>
    <published>2022-03-03T12:19:38.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-03-06T04:15:37.231Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="What-made-you-smile-today"><a href="#What-made-you-smile-today" class="headerlink" title="What made you smile today?"></a><strong>What made you smile today?</strong></h4><p><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);"><strong>Let us walk together</strong></span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);">23.7k Views · 2.1k Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p><strong>Many little girls have admiration for their fathers.</strong> </p><p>It will be <u>a tough nut to crack</u> when she grows up seeing not all men are like her daddy. This made me smile. No matter your dad is trying to impress you or just be a <u>goofy</u> clown to make you laugh, they are our heroes. She is one proud princess, who knows her daddy will be her forever protector. This is very precious!</p><p>Dad showing off his skill to the surprise of his little daughter in Melbourne Australia …(circa - 1940)</p><img src="https://gitee.com/zjloved/blogimg/raw/master/img/image-20220303202107547.png" alt="" style="zoom:80%;" /><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>待更新</span></p></details><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong>Victoria Ng:</strong></em><br>I was my dad’s favorite and my parents treated me like a princess growing up. I still feel that this privilege is only made possible because i had good parents. They didn’t have a lot to teach and guide, but they gave us everything we needed. Even when I am grown up my dad still treats me like this princess and <u>pampers</u> me.</p></blockquote><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>a hard&#x2F;tough nut to crack</strong>: a difficult problem or situation 棘手的问题，难办的事: Celtic have lost only once this season and will be a tough nut to crack. 凯尔特人队本赛季只输过一场，不好对付。</li><li><strong>goofy</strong>: &#x2F;‘guːfɪ&#x2F; stupid or silly 愚蠢的，傻的: A goofy grin spread across her face when she saw the card. 她看到卡片，脸上露出了傻傻的笑容。</li><li><strong>pamper</strong>: &#x2F;‘pæmpə&#x2F; to look after someone very kindly, for example by giving them the things that they want and making them feel warm and comfortable 宠，娇惯; 呵护: She spent her childhood as the pampered daughter of a wealthy family. 她出身于一个富裕家庭，从小娇生惯养。</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGdYaO">https://qr.ae/pGdYaO</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">Many little girls have admiration for their fathers.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why do schools teach algebra, trigonometry, and calculus when nobody even uses it?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/03/03/2022-03-03-Why-do-schools-teach-algebra,-trigonometry,-and-calculus-when-nobody-even-uses-it/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/03/03/2022-03-03-Why-do-schools-teach-algebra,-trigonometry,-and-calculus-when-nobody-even-uses-it/</id>
    <published>2022-03-03T12:09:08.925Z</published>
    <updated>2022-03-06T04:15:18.346Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="Why-do-schools-teach-algebra-trigonometry-and-calculus-when-nobody-even-uses-it"><a href="#Why-do-schools-teach-algebra-trigonometry-and-calculus-when-nobody-even-uses-it" class="headerlink" title="Why do schools teach algebra, trigonometry, and calculus when nobody even uses it?"></a><strong>Why do schools teach algebra, trigonometry, and calculus when nobody even uses it?</strong></h4><p><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'><strong>Thomas B Walsh</strong>, Author, Blogger, and Retired Fortune 100 Executive</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'>219.1K views · 4.1K Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>There’s an old joke.</p><p><strong>Student</strong>: Teacher, I don’t see why I have to take Algebra or Trig. Does anybody ever use this stuff?</p><p><strong>Teacher</strong>: You won’t, but the smart kids will.</p><p>I have been retired for a long time now, but I hired a lot of college grads in my day. We received LOTS of resumes.</p><p><strong>To <u>pare</u> that stack down, I would look for candidates who had taken math and&#x2F;or coding classes, not The History of Rock and Roll.</strong></p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>待更新</span></p></details><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Robert-M-Wallis">Robert M. Wallis</a></strong></p><p>Students would complain back when I taught math, claiming they would never use it real life. I told them that in real life, they would only use 10% of it. They would get excited, then I would tell them the only problem was they would have no idea which 10% it was going to be.</p></blockquote><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>pare sth. down</strong>: to reduce something, especially by making a lot of small reductions〔逐步〕削减，减少: The list was pared down for the final interviews. 名单上的人数逐步减少，以确定最后面试人选。</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGdAm8">https://qr.ae/pGdAm8</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">To pare that stack down, I would look for candidates who had taken math and(or) coding classes</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Are clouds actually soft to touch, or is that a lie?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/03/03/2022-03-03-Are-clouds-actually-soft-to-touch,-or-is-that-a-lie/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/03/03/2022-03-03-Are-clouds-actually-soft-to-touch,-or-is-that-a-lie/</id>
    <published>2022-03-03T04:16:07.714Z</published>
    <updated>2022-03-05T02:23:04.901Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="Are-clouds-actually-soft-to-touch-or-is-that-a-lie"><a href="#Are-clouds-actually-soft-to-touch-or-is-that-a-lie" class="headerlink" title="Are clouds actually soft to touch, or is that a lie?"></a><strong>Are clouds actually soft to touch, or is that a lie?</strong></h4><p><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'><em><strong>Rich DeAngelis</strong></em>, Electronic engineer, test, manufacturing and design in many industries.</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style='color: rgb(0, 128, 255);'>244.8K views · 11.6K Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>Are clouds actually soft to touch, or is that a lie?</p><p>If you’ve ever been outside on a foggy day, you know what it feels like. Pretty much like nothing.</p><p>Fog is nothing more than a cloud at a low enough level that we are inside the cloud. You may feel a bit of the moisture if you wave your hands around in it and it is dense enough. But you will never be able to “feel” it in the traditional way because it <u>exerts</u> no more pressure on your senses beyond what clear, dry air does.</p><img src="https://gitee.com/zjloved/blogimg/raw/master/img/image-20220303121724756.png" alt="" style="zoom:80%;" /><p>This is why airplanes and jets can fly through clouds and not take any damage. Traveling 500+ mph would destroy them if the cloud exerted any force on the aircraft.</p><p>The only danger here is not seeing another aircraft or mountain or radio tower - those would hurt!</p><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong>Andrew McGregor:</strong></em><br>What a lovely picture of that plane’s <u>wake</u>!</p><p><em><strong>Henry K.O. Norman:</strong></em><br>Riddle: What’s the difference between a cloud and fog?<br>Answer: A fog, we walk or drive through. Clouds, we fly through.</p></blockquote><p><span style='color: rgb(70, 118, 217);'>▌</span><strong><span style='color: rgb(136, 136, 136);'>词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>exert</strong>: &#x2F;ɪg’zɜːt&#x2F; to use your power, influence etc in order to make something happen运用〔权力〕; 施加〔影响力〕</li><li><strong>wake</strong>: the track made behind a boat as it moves through the water〔船开过后留下的〕航迹，尾流</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGdYZQ">https://qr.ae/pGdYZQ</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">Fog is nothing more than a cloud at a low enough level that we are inside the cloud.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Quora" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/"/>
    
    <category term="文选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What are some psychological facts that people don&#39;t know?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/02/26/2022-02-26-What-are-some-psychological-facts-that-people-dont-know/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/02/26/2022-02-26-What-are-some-psychological-facts-that-people-dont-know/</id>
    <published>2022-02-26T08:53:43.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-02-27T09:02:51.771Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="What-are-some-psychological-facts-that-people-don’t-know"><a href="#What-are-some-psychological-facts-that-people-don’t-know" class="headerlink" title="What are some psychological facts that people don’t know?"></a><strong>What are some psychological facts that people don’t know?</strong></h4><p><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);"><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Matt-Schlenker">Matt Schlenker</a></strong>, B.A. Neuroscience, Columbia University (2014)</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);">2M Views · 85.9k Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>The Ben Franklin Effect.</p><p><strong>Ben Franklin unlocked the secret to getting other people to like you.</strong> Most of us have been <u>conditioned</u> to think that the way to get someone to like us is by doing nice little favors for them, thereby demonstrating that we are a thoughtful and dependable person. Old Benji thought differently.</p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>翻译待更新</span></p></details><p>Franklin once had a very powerful political <u>rival</u> who was <u>hellbent on</u> making his life miserable. Franklin knew that it would be beneficial to have this man on his side, but instead of <u>groveling</u> for his approval, he took a <u>counter-intuitive</u> approach. He knew his rival was in possession of a very rare and valuable book, and simply asked him to borrow it. After a few days, he returned it with a thank you note and, surprisingly, his rival became his friend.</p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>翻译待更新</span></p></details><p>What Franklin <u>tapped into</u> is a well-known psychological principle known as <u>cognitive dissonance</u>. Basically, cognitive dissonance is the tension that results from having two contradictory beliefs in our mind at the same time. This stress is uncomfortable, so we automatically alter one of our beliefs to conform with the other to resolve this conflict.</p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>翻译待更新</span></p></details><p>In the case of Franklin, his rival held the belief: “I do not like Benjamin Franklin.” Upon doing him the favor, however, he was forced to come to terms with another belief: “It’s a pain in the ass to do favors for other people, so I only do favors for people I like.” These two beliefs are in conflict, and since he cannot un-loan the book, he was forced to soften and eventually reverse his ill-will towards Franklin.</p><p>The secret of the Benjamin Franklin effect is this: <strong>If you want people to like you, ask them to do favors for you.</strong></p><details>  <summary><span style='color:white;font-weight:bold'>展开翻译</span></summary>  <p><span style='color:red;font-size:12pt'>翻译待更新</span></p></details><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Feifei-Wang-6">Feifei Wang</a></strong></p><p>I remember a similar experiment: Two group of people are asked to participate an activity. Group A is participate for free; while Group B had to pay a small amount of money to participate. Afterwards, the participants were asked about their feeling towards the activity they’ve asked to perform, are they fun? Do you like it? etc. Group A (free user), give pretty neutral feedback; while Group B (paid user) give more favorable feedback, they genuinely believe they like what they did. It’s the same cognitive dissonance.</p></blockquote><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>condition</strong>: to make a person or an animal think or behave in a certain way by influencing or training them over a period of time〔通过影响或训练〕使习惯于，使适应</li><li><strong>rival</strong>: &#x2F;ˈraivəl&#x2F; a person, group, or organization that you compete with in sport, business, a fight etc 对手，竞争者</li><li><strong>hellbent on</strong>: &#x2F;‘helbent&#x2F; very determined to do something, especially something that other people do not approve of 坚决的，不顾一切的</li><li><strong>grovel</strong>: &#x2F;ˈgrɔvəl&#x2F; to praise someone a lot or behave with a lot of respect towards them because you think that they are important and will be able to help you in some way – used to show disapproval〔因有求于人而〕卑躬屈膝〔含贬义〕</li><li><strong>counter-intuitive</strong>: &#x2F;ɪn’tjuːɪtɪv&#x2F; contrary to what one would naturally expect 与情理中的预料相反的; 反直觉的: His solution to the problem is counter-intuitive. 他解决这问题的方法是出人意表的.</li><li><strong>tap into</strong>: to make as much use as possible of the ideas, experience, knowledge etc that a group of people has 利用，采用〔思想、经验、知识等〕</li><li><strong>cognitive dissonance</strong>: &#x2F;ˈkɔɡnitiv ‘dɪs(ə)nəns&#x2F; 认知不和谐; 认知失调论; 认知失调: Cognitive dissonance: this describes the act of holding two conflicting beliefs at the same time. 认知不和谐：这指的是同时持有两种互相矛盾的想法的行为。</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGQ6kR">https://qr.ae/pGQ6kR</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">If you want people to like you, ask them to do favors for you.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Who is responsible for the Ukraine Crisis?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/02/26/2022-02-26-Who-is-responsible-for-the-Ukraine-Crisis/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/02/26/2022-02-26-Who-is-responsible-for-the-Ukraine-Crisis/</id>
    <published>2022-02-26T06:15:40.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-02-26T08:53:32.038Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="Who-is-responsible-for-the-Ukraine-Crisis"><a href="#Who-is-responsible-for-the-Ukraine-Crisis" class="headerlink" title="Who is responsible for the Ukraine Crisis?"></a><strong>Who is responsible for the Ukraine Crisis?</strong></h4><p><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);"><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Toma%C5%BE-Vargazon">Tomaž Vargazon</a></strong></span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);">47.9k Views · 2.2k Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>Russian forces occupy <u>portion</u> of Ukraine.</p><p>How can a crisis that began with Russian soldiers entering Ukraine and Russia <u>annexing</u> a portion of Ukrainian territory be responsibility of Ukraine?</p><p>Better yet, how did we get to a place when one must explain that Russian forces taking over portions of Ukraine isn’t the responsibility of Ukraine, but Russia?</p><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Rob-Heusdens">Rob Heusdens</a></strong><br>It began with civilian peaceful protests, and was answered by Ukrain with military violence. And it all started with the maidan <u>coup</u>, US organizing a new Ukrain government without first holding regular elections for a new president, which people in Donbass rejected as legal government, because the coup was illegal.</p><p><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Tim-Doherty-9">Tim Doherty</a></strong><br>One of my Russian-speaking friends just told me that Putin had addressed the nation and he’s saying that NATO is about to invade Ukraine and that they want to bring nukes to Ukraine to control the Russian state. I have to admit that his narrative, as crazy as it sounds to us, may be effective.</p></blockquote><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>portion</strong>: a part of something larger, especially a part that is different from the other parts〔某物的〕一部分</li><li><strong>annex</strong>: &#x2F;ə’neks&#x2F; to take control of a country or area next to your own, especially by using force并吞，〔尤指通过使用武力〕兼并，霸占〔国家或领土〕: The Baltic republics were annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940. 1940 年波罗的海诸共和国被苏联吞并。</li><li><strong>coup</strong>: a sudden and sometimes violent attempt by citizens or the army to take control of the government（军事）政变</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGQ6F6">https://qr.ae/pGQ6F6</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">Russian forces occupy portion of Ukraine.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Quora" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/"/>
    
    <category term="文选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What is the most curious door you have ever seen?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/02/26/2022-02-26-What-is-the-most-curious-door-you-have-ever-seen/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/02/26/2022-02-26-What-is-the-most-curious-door-you-have-ever-seen/</id>
    <published>2022-02-26T06:04:38.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-02-26T06:16:01.912Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="What-is-the-most-curious-door-you-have-ever-seen"><a href="#What-is-the-most-curious-door-you-have-ever-seen" class="headerlink" title="What is the most curious door you have ever seen?"></a><strong>What is the most curious door you have ever seen?</strong></h4><p><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);"><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Humberto-Perozo">Humberto Perozo</a></strong> · </span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);">702.2k Views · 41.2k Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>Well, I think a very curious one is this door:</p><img src="https://gitee.com/zjloved/blogimg/raw/master/img/image-20220226140703615.png" style="zoom: 80%;" /><p>You may wonder why this door is so thin.</p><p>Well, this door is from the <u>monastery</u> of Portugal and it has this characteristic because <strong>it was used to keep the monks thin.</strong></p><p>This door of 2 meters high and only 32 centimeters wide was the entrance to the dining room.</p><img src="https://gitee.com/zjloved/blogimg/raw/master/img/image-20220226140815389.png" alt="" style="zoom:80%;" /><p>It was built to prevent overweight <u>gluttonous</u> monks who did not stop eating.</p><p>If they gained weight, it would be impossible for them to enter the dining hall to eat, so they would be forced to lose weight.</p><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong>Paul Taylor:</strong></em><br>I presume some greedy monks, had dinner, <u>stuffed</u> themselves then had to stay there till they were slim enough to leave!</p><p><em><strong>Ralph King:</strong></em><br>This could be an old suggestion for a very modern problem. Now, which dining hall to start installing them at?</p></blockquote><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>monastery</strong>: &#x2F;‘mɑnəstɛri&#x2F; a place where monks live 寺院，修道院</li><li><strong>gluttonous</strong>: &#x2F;ˋɡlʌtnəs&#x2F; very greedy for food 贪吃的; 贪嘴的</li><li><strong>stuffed</strong>: completely full, so that you cannot eat any more 吃饱了的: No, no dessert, I’m stuffed.不，不要甜点了，我吃饱了。</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGQ6YE">https://qr.ae/pGQ6YE</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">it was used to keep the monks thin.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Quora" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/"/>
    
    <category term="文选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What is the most offended you&#39;ve ever been?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/02/25/2022-02-25-What-is-the-most-offended-youve-ever-been/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/02/25/2022-02-25-What-is-the-most-offended-youve-ever-been/</id>
    <published>2022-02-25T08:33:17.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-02-26T00:11:42.986Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="What-is-the-most-offended-you’ve-ever-been"><a href="#What-is-the-most-offended-you’ve-ever-been" class="headerlink" title="What is the most offended you’ve ever been?"></a><strong>What is the most offended you’ve ever been?</strong></h4><p><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);"><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Elizabeth-Sabella-1">Elizabeth Sabella</a></strong>, Former Retired school district administrator at Bristol Township School</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);">302k Views · 8.6k Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>About 40 years ago, my mother suggested I send my 10 year old son to my sister’s house for the summer. Mom believed that grandson needed to be “<u>straightened out</u>“. I <u>was crushed to</u> think I wasn’t an <u>adequate</u> mother in her eyes. </p><p>My parents approved of my sister’s style of child-rearing. She had 4 daughters that she potty trained in 1 day with a wooden spoon. They ran <u>diaper</u> free all day, then when they relieved themselves, she hit them with the spoon and sat them on the pot. She carried that spoon everywhere she went, and had no problem hitting them wherever and whenever they misbehaved. Her primary goal was <u>obedience</u>. </p><p><strong>I allowed my kids to express their feelings, but made it clear that they still had to do what I told them to do.</strong> My family thought my kids were undisciplined and that I was unable to control them.</p><p>I refused to follow their child rearing methods, and I was comfortable with my style. <strong>I am proud of the <u>fine</u> men my sons turned out to be, and happy that they grew up knowing that their feelings were valid, and they were heard.</strong></p><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Michelle-A-Rivera-2">Michelle A Rivera</a></strong></p><p>I’m a dog trainer and when you wrote about how she let them run around all day with no pants and then hit them I was horrified. But, I let my two sons run around with just a long t-shirt on and whenever they started to pee I picked them up and put them on the little potty. I really didn’t think it was a bad way to potty train. But positive reinforcement is powerful and when they finally got the concept they got praise and a sticker. It’s how I trained puppies, and it’s the only way I knew how. The point is to catch them in the act and show them the proper place to do that. It worked pretty well.</p></blockquote><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>straighten sth. out</strong>: to deal with problems or a confused situation and make it better, especially by organizing things 解决〔问题〕; 整顿〔混乱情况〕: There are several financial problems that need to be straightened out quickly. 有几个财务问题需要迅速解决。</li><li><strong>crush</strong>: to make someone feel extremely upset or shocked 使非常伤心; 使震惊: Sara was crushed by their insults. 萨拉因他们的侮辱而非常伤心。</li><li><strong>adequate</strong>: fairly good but not excellent 尚可的，过得去的: Her performance was adequate but lacked originality. 她的表演还过得去，但缺乏独创性。</li><li><strong>rear</strong>: to look after a person or animal until they are fully grown 养育，抚养〔孩子〕; 饲养〔动物〕: It’s a good place to rear young children. 这是个抚养年幼孩子的好地方。</li><li><strong>diaper</strong>: a piece of soft cloth or soft paper that is put between a baby’s legs and fastened around its waist to hold liquid and solid waste 尿布，尿片</li><li><strong>obedience</strong>: when someone does what they are told to do, or what a law, rule etc says they must do 服从，顺从，遵从</li><li><strong>fine</strong>: satisfactory or acceptable 令人满意的，可以接受的</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGQxL5">https://qr.ae/pGQxL5</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">I am proud of the fine men my sons turned out to be</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Quora" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/"/>
    
    <category term="文选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/Quora/%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What are some unwritten social rules everyone should know?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/02/22/2022-02-22-What-are-some-unwritten-social-rules-everyone-should-know/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/02/22/2022-02-22-What-are-some-unwritten-social-rules-everyone-should-know/</id>
    <published>2022-02-22T10:40:12.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-02-26T10:29:47.338Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="What-are-some-unwritten-social-rules-everyone-should-know"><a href="#What-are-some-unwritten-social-rules-everyone-should-know" class="headerlink" title="What are some unwritten social rules everyone should know?"></a><strong>What are some unwritten social rules everyone should know?</strong></h4><p><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);"><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Alex-Ferman-5">Alex Ferman</a></strong>, Passionate Writer, CA (2013 - present)</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);">292.6k Views · 6.7k Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><ol><li><p>1+1 &#x3D; 3 if you don’t use the condom.</p></li><li><p>Alcohol increase size of the “SEND” button by 89%.</p></li><li><p>Never underestimate the power of stupid people in large groups.</p></li><li><p><strong>Sometimes we create our own heartbreaks through expectations.</strong></p></li><li><p>Life is too short to be with the wrong person.</p></li><li><p>Just because you love them, it doesn’t mean they’re right for you.</p></li><li><p>Feelings that come back are feelings that never left.</p></li><li><p>Everything’s not as easy as getting fat.</p></li><li><p>Even a bad day is just 24 hours.</p></li><li><p>It’s not your job to fix people.</p></li></ol><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Littlebigmous">Littlebigmous</a></strong></p><p>Be kind and be nice… but do not expect others to treat you in the same way. We all have our demons. If you encounter someone who is <u>entangled</u> with their demons, be nice to yourself as it is not your battle to fight and walk away.</p></blockquote><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>entangle</strong>: o involve someone in an argument, a relationship, or a situation that is difficult to escape from 使卷入，使陷入</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGQMt1">https://qr.ae/pGQMt1</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">Sometimes we create our own heartbreaks through expectations.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How do I make my 14-year-old son more manly?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/02/21/2022-02-21-How-do-I-make-my-14-year-old-son-more-manly/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/02/21/2022-02-21-How-do-I-make-my-14-year-old-son-more-manly/</id>
    <published>2022-02-21T03:16:20.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-02-26T10:29:55.251Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="How-do-I-make-my-14-year-old-son-more-manly"><a href="#How-do-I-make-my-14-year-old-son-more-manly" class="headerlink" title="How do I make my 14-year-old son more manly?"></a><strong>How do I make my 14-year-old son more manly?</strong></h4><p><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);"><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Chris-Clarke-10">Chris Clarke</a></strong>, Studying ancient Hebrew</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);">1.3M Views · 1.1k Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>By being one yourself (sigh). </p><p>This type of question triggers me, mainly because my dad’s focus was the same thing, but yet he never taught me anything because he was never taught how to be more manly. So he expected me to be it, yet what child can learn without a template, what <u>apprentice</u> can learn without a teacher, lest the apprentice goes down the wrong path and find another teacher who teaches them the wrong way.</p><p>Become secure in yourself, talk to him, your wife, your friends, your family, your neighbors, your coworkers, your communities and everyone under the sun the way you want your son to. And I promise you, you don’t have to say a single word to your son, he will see you are successful and <u>mirror</u> you, because he’ll want to receive the blessing that are receiving down this path.</p><p>And tell him the truth… you’re learning how to do it as well, and you’ll figure it out together - <strong>like father and son.</strong></p><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Rupert-Cheek">Rupert Cheek</a></strong></em></p><p>and LISTEN (to him)!</p></blockquote><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>apprentice</strong>: <u>&#x2F;ə’prɛntɪs&#x2F;</u> someone who works for an employer for a fixed period of time in order to learn a particular skill or job 学徒，徒弟: She works in the hairdresser’s as an apprentice. 她在美发店当学徒。</li><li><strong>mirror</strong>: if one thing mirrors another, it is very similar to it and may seem to copy or represent it反映〔相似的情况等〕: Henry’s sad smile mirrored that of his son. 亨利脸上那苦涩的笑容跟他儿子一模一样。</li><li><strong>like father and son</strong>:  used to say that a boy behaves like his father, especially when this behavior is bad 有其父必有其子</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-make-my-14-year-old-son-more-manly/answer/Chris-Clarke-10">https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-make-my-14-year-old-son-more-manly/answer/Chris-Clarke-10</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">you&#39;ll figure it out together - like father and son.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What makes you feel grateful?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/02/15/2022-02-15-What-makes-you-feel-grateful/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/02/15/2022-02-15-What-makes-you-feel-grateful/</id>
    <published>2022-02-15T13:13:46.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-02-26T10:30:01.525Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="What-makes-you-feel-grateful"><a href="#What-makes-you-feel-grateful" class="headerlink" title="What makes you feel grateful?"></a><strong>What makes you feel grateful?</strong></h4><p><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);"><em><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Inam-Tanveer-Talks">Inam Tanveer Talks</a></strong></em>, Former Medical officer</span></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);">64.5k Views · 5.9k Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>The rich <u>industrialist</u> was horrified to find the fisherman Iying beside his boat, smoking a pipe.</p><p>‘Why aren’t you out fishing?’ asked the industrialist.</p><p>‘Because I have caught enough fish for the day.’</p><p>‘Why don’t you catch some more?’</p><p>‘What would I do with them?’</p><p>‘You could earn more money. Then you could have a motor fitted to your boat to go into deeper waters and catch more fish. Then you would have enough money to buy <u>nylon</u> nets. These would bring you more fish and more money. Soon you would have enough money own two boats…maybe even a fleet of boats. Then you would be a rich man like me.’</p><p>‘What would I do then?’</p><p>‘Then you could sit back and enjoy life.’</p><p><strong>‘What do you think I’m doing right now?’</strong></p><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Brian-Mead-5">Brian Mead</a></strong></em></p><p>This is my attitude towards work. Why would I ever think myself poor? I am content with what I have, I am fed, sheltered, and so on. I have things I enjoy, and I have people who truly care about me. I am not poor in any measure.</p></blockquote><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>industrialist</strong>: a person who owns or runs a factory or industrial company 工业家，实业家</li><li><strong>nylon</strong>: a strong artificial material that is used to make plastics, clothes, rope etc 尼龙</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://qr.ae/pGjDFJ">https://qr.ae/pGjDFJ</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">Life is a journey, not a race.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What is the biggest lie society has taught you to believe?</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/02/15/2022-02-15-What-is-the-biggest-lie-society-has-taught-you-to-believe/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/02/15/2022-02-15-What-is-the-biggest-lie-society-has-taught-you-to-believe/</id>
    <published>2022-02-15T11:20:51.001Z</published>
    <updated>2022-02-26T10:30:09.982Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="What-is-the-biggest-lie-society-has-taught-you-to-believe"><a href="#What-is-the-biggest-lie-society-has-taught-you-to-believe" class="headerlink" title="What is the biggest lie society has taught you to believe?"></a><strong>What is the biggest lie society has taught you to believe?</strong></h4><p><em><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);"><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Hector-Quintanilla">Hector Quintanilla</a></strong></span></em></p><blockquote><p><strong><span style="color: rgb(0, 128, 255);">411.9k Views · 7.8k Upvotes</span></strong></p></blockquote><p>LIE: “Work hard and you’ll achieve financial freedom.”</p><p>Yes, it’s a popular belief that hard work pays off.</p><p>And it does.</p><p>In fact, hard work is <u>non-negotiable</u>.</p><p>But… there’s a LIMIT to hard work.</p><p>We all have the same 24 hours in a day, and I can guarantee you will meet these limits EVERY single day.</p><p>But, if Jeff Bezos grew his net worth by $75 billion in 2020 — does that mean he worked 1,000,000 X harder than someone making $75K a year?</p><p>Obviously no!</p><p>So yes, there’s hard work, but hard work will always face our human limitations. <strong>Then, there’s</strong> <strong>smart</strong> <strong>work, where there are no boundaries!</strong></p><p>If you’ve hit the “roof” of hard work, you will only find further growth until you change HOW you work.</p><p><strong>LIE: Work hard and you’ll achieve financial freedom.</strong></p><p>Yes, work hard, but stop trying to “work” your way to wealth.</p><p>Financial success is found in working smarter and that is only found through the experience and wisdom of others.</p><p><strong>Leveraging other people’s knowledge is your shortcut to make a good living.</strong></p><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">评论:</span></strong></p><blockquote><p><em><strong><a href="https://www.quora.com/profile/Quinn-Copeland">Quinn Copeland</a></strong></em>:</p><p>“Work hard” is meant to reference putting in effort, not long hours of manual labor. The point is that its not enough to have a good idea, you have to be focused and put the work in to <em>execute it</em>.</p></blockquote><p><span style="color: rgb(70, 118, 217);">▌</span><strong><span style="color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">词汇:</span></strong></p><blockquote><ul><li><strong>non-negotiable</strong>: a non-negotiable principle or belief is one that you refuse to discuss or change 不可谈判的，无商量余地的; 不能更改的: He emphasized that the government’s anti-nuclear position was non-negotiable. 他强调政府的反核立场是不可动摇的。</li><li><strong>leverage</strong>: to spread or use resources (&#x3D;money, skills, buildings etc that an organization has available), ideas etc again in several different ways or in different parts of a company, system etc充分利用〔资源、观点等〕</li></ul></blockquote><p><a href="https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-biggest-lie-society-has-taught-you-to-believe/answer/Hector-Quintanilla">https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-biggest-lie-society-has-taught-you-to-believe/answer/Hector-Quintanilla</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">Leveraging other people&#39;s knowledge is your shortcut to make a good living.</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/categories/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Quora文选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Quora%E6%96%87%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="★精选" scheme="http://example.com/tags/%E2%98%85%E7%B2%BE%E9%80%89/"/>
    
    <category term="2022年" scheme="http://example.com/tags/2022%E5%B9%B4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
